lifedaily.com 2017-06-06

# LifeDaily

**Life Daily Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us at Life Daily. The following describes the Privacy Policy for our http://www.lifedaily.com/ website (“Site”). This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Life Daily (“we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on the Site and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Site, the “Services”).

You agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy by virtue of accessing or using our website on any computer, mobile phone, tablet or other device (collectively, “Device”). If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits our customers who are California residents to request certain information about disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

Email:  info@LifeDaily.com

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, our website will not knowingly collect or maintain information from children are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. 

Under our Terms of Service and Conditions of Use, children under 18 are not allowed to use our website and access our services. It is not our intention to offer products or services to minors. 

**Information We Collect**

  1. **Non-Personal Information**

When visiting our website we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address used to access our website, browser type, operating system, the specific webpages visited during your connection, and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other clickstream data. This information is used to analyze trends, administer our website, track users’ movement, and gather broad demographic information for internal use such as statistical assessments, research, website improvement, and other purposes. 

Like many commercial websites, we analyze how visitors use our Site through what is known as “cookie” technology. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer when you access the Site and allows us to recognize you each time you visit the Site. Cookies are a key means of improving user experience by allows us to customize your use of our website. Simple information is transferred to your computer to allow the content and experience at http://www.lifedaily.com/ to reflect your actions, preferences, and so on. For example, we may use cookies to: (i) allow you to use the Site without having to re-enter a user name and password; (ii) enhance or personalize your Site usage; (iii) monitor Site usage; (iv) manage the Site; and (v) improve the Site and our products and services. You should simply make the assumption our website uses cookies, and note that you are free to make adjustments in your web browser to disable these or otherwise receive notification of cookies so you can take whatever desired action you so choose. Please understand that refusing cookies may cripple some of our website features and render some aspects useless to you. 

This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.

We may also use web beacons on the Site, in our emails and in our advertisements on other websites. Web beacons are tiny graphic images that are used to collect information about your Site visit, such as the pages you view and the features you use, as well as information about whether you open and/or act upon one of our emails or advertisements. We may also collect the URL of the website you visited immediately before coming to the Site. Web beacons help us analyze our Site visitors’ behavior and measure the effectiveness of the Site and our advertising. We may work with service providers, such as Google Analytics, that help us track, collect and analyze this information. 

We may combine the non-personal information we collect, such as through cookies and web beacons, with other information we have collected from you.

  1. **Personal Information**

We collect personal information from you when you submit it to us, including by (i) creating an Account with us and providing us with your username, password and email address; (ii) emailing us; (iii) signing up with us to be an author; (iv) participating in promotions, surveys, email newsletters or other features of the Site; (v) placing an order through us; and (vi) communicating with us directly through the Site. Such personal information may include your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, credit card information and other applicable information.  If you access the Services through Facebook credentials, we may automatically collect certain information, such as your name, picture, and email address. We will use all information available through Facebook in accordance with Facebook’s policies and your preferences selected through Facebook. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, when we feel such information is important. You may unsubscribe from these messages through your Account settings, although we reserve the right to contact you even if you unsubscribe when we believe it is necessary, such as for Account recovery purposes.

At times, you will be fully aware of information received, as you are the direct source providing it. Purchases necessarily involve collecting certain information, such as credit card information, Paypal addresses, your physical address for billing and/or shipping, phone number, and so on. Refusing to provide some of this information may lead to us being unable to provide you with the products or services you’ve requested. 

**User Content**

Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments. All content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties, as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Handling of Personal Information**

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (i) to complete a transaction (including fulfillment of orders); (ii) to communicate with you regarding our Services or to notify you about other products and services; (iii) to review Site usage and operations; (iv) to address problems with the Site, our business or our services; (v) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business; (vi) to monitor the site for compliance with our [Terms of Use](http://www.lifedaily.com/terms-conditions/) and the law; and (vii) to contact you with Site updates, newsletters and other information and promotional materials from us.

If you change your mind and no longer wish to receive our email updates, you can opt-out at any time by sending an email to:  [info@LifeDaily.com](mailto:info@LifeDaily.com), or by mail to: 

384 RXR Plaza

Uniondale NY, 11556

Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving such marketing emails from us, you may still receive email messages regarding any orders your place or service notifications.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies and service providers, to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) to our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third parties who may contact you with their own offers; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Site Terms of Use or of our other rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to a legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order) and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (5) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. 

Some of your activity on and through the Services is public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, content you have posted or shared publicly on the Site or otherwise through the services, such as written posts, comments, or other submissions by you to the Site. In addition, if you share information with third parties not functioning as a service provider to us that puts your information beyond our control and becomes subject to the policy the third party has in place. Please also remember that by choosing to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, you make your information publicly available. Users reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through the Services.

Our primary intention for collecting personal and private information from you is simply to conduct our business. We can use this internally to better serve you. Accordingly, we see no reason to share your personal information to other parties and outside interests unless you have authorized us to do so. Of course, there are instances where your information is stored with third party service providers, such as email service providers, as they provide services that are industry-leading in quality and security and are far more beneficial to our end user than attempting such services in-house. However, you are never required to deal with any such third party directly, they are limited in how they use your information, and they cannot sell or transfer it to others in any way. 

You may access other Third Party Services through the Site, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party Services from within the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information we collect in connection with our Services.  

We may also share aggregate, non-personal information about Site users with third parties. We may share this information about our website visitors as a whole, not individually, with our partners, service providers, and other third parties with whom we conduct business for various purposes, in our sole discretion. In addition, these third parties may share with us information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

**Security**

Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to help prevent unauthorized access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.

We maintain reasonable and appropriate measures designed to maintain information we collect in a secure manner.  We have taken certain physical, electronic, and administrative steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Site visitors.  Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances.

**Interest-Based Advertising**

The Site may include third party advertising and links to other websites. These third party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their own behalf, sometimes use technology to send, directly to your browser, advertisements that appear on our website. They may also use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect anonymous information in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. To learn more about behavioral advertising or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). Note that electing to opt-out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. In addition, note that that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, may use cookies to serve ads on this http://www.lifedaily.com/ website. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website, including past visits, as well as other websites on the internet. 

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. 

**International Users**

The Site may be accessed by an international audience.  By visiting the Site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information may be processed for the purposes identified in this policy.  In addition, such data may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction and in jurisdictions which may have less stringent privacy practices than your own.  By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data. 

**Third Party Websites**

This Site contains links to third-party websites that are not affiliated with Life Daily, and which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. Once you leave the site or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or Terms of Service. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites and encourage you to read their privacy statements before disclosing any personal information.  Please contact those websites directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

**CHANGE NOTICE:** As with any of our administrative and legal notice pages, the contents of this page can and will change over time. Accordingly, this page could read differently as of your very next visit. These changes are necessitated, and carried out by Life Daily, in order to protect you and our http://www.lifedaily.com/ website. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If this page is important to you, you should check back frequently as no other notice of changed content will be provided either before or after the change takes effect. 

**QUESTIONS/COMMENTS/CONCERNS:** If you have any questions about the contents of this page, or simply wish to reach us for any other reason, you may do so by using our Contact information. 

**Effective Date** : February 12, 2016
